Gabriel Tome

Web Developer / Product Designer / Software Engineer

Profile

Web Developer and Product Designer with over 10 years experience on tech industry, have experience in developing high performance websites (A++) and clean interfaces.

Blending minimalistic style web design, user experience and web development to create stunning products always seeking high convertion rate.

Experience with Web Development, UX/UI and SEO.

My main skills are related to creating websites following good software engineering practices.

I graduated as a Information Systems in 2012.

Specialties: Web applications, Product Design, User Experience and User Interface

Skills: Figma, HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Node, Git, Scrum

Experience

Co-founder | Full-Stack Developer

Product Design | Web Development | Alphon Technology | 03/2020 - present As a Full-Stack Web Developer, I work on the Alphon Technology to build and maintain her main websites and Landing Pages in high performance with scores > (A++) and 95%. With growth mindset, we help our clients reach over +500k in sells, with PPC Adversiting strategies.

I develop the main website and the others landing pages, with Gmetrix score always above 90% and A++. Landing Pages for reach qualified leads.

Main technologies: Figma, Webflow, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Google Tag Manager

Full-Stack Software Developer | Freelancer | 2010 – present

www.gabrielt.dev

Developing software and interfaces with the best practices.

Double-diamond and scrum methodology.

Main technologies: Webflow, Figma, HTML, CSS, GIT, React, Node

Android Developer | Protege | 04/2013 - 07/2013

Developing an app to track employees and payments with cards.

Main technologies: Java, Android, CSS, HTML, MySql.

Support Analyst | Funorte | 01/2013 - 04/2013

Mobile and Web Developer Intern | Unica Technology | 11/2010 - 03/2011

Main technologies: Android, HTML, CSS, PHP, MySQL, jQuery.

Its main purpose is to create a tech startup to offer digital solutions. I developed the website interface and the app.

Education

Faculdade de Computação (FACOMP) | 2008 - 2012

B.S., Information Systems

Pontifícia Universidade Católica de Minas Gerais (PUC-MG) | 2015 - 2017

Specialization in Web Application Development

Courses

```
2014 - Web Design Bruno Ávila - 60 Hrr
```

2011 - Agile with Scrum - 16 Hrs

2017 - Be MEAN - Mongo, React, Angular, Node - webschool - 120 Hrs

2017 - JavaScript Course - Udemy

2018 - React - Origamid

2021 - Ethereum Solidity Course - Udemy

2021 - Yield Hacking / Yield Farmimg - 8h

2022 - Solidity Bootcamp - Codesign

2022 - Javascript DAO Bootcamp - Web3DAO

2022 - NFT with Javascript Bootcamp - Web3DAO

Conference/Organization

2021 ~ present - Web3dev DAO member

2020 ~ present – Developer_DAO genesis member

2010/2011 ~ Campus Party Brasil

2010/2012 ~ Instructor Java EE - Basic to Advanced, Minas Gerais - BR.

2011/2012 ~ Instructor – Creating Android App, Minas Gerais - BR.

Publications

1. LISBOA, G. T. - Understanding the architecture of the Android Platform and the development of an application.. 2012, Minas Gerais, Brazil.